Can y'all feel it? 2024 is just ushering in a release of realism. It's happening,
whether you like it or not. So I suggest everybody get on board, you know? And when I say get on
board, I mean really reevaluate. Look around at the people in your life. Look into yourself
and really ask yourself, what are your metrics of truth, of love, of friendship, of relationships,
of business? Like it's time to do a real reassessment, okay? Forget the exit interview.
This is the entrance interview into a new era and it's going to start with you. So get busy.
We ain't walking into the new year. We done been dropped into the new year. Yes. Like we coming
from a plane and they like, good luck. You better find that parachute handle. Just ignore the fact
that my hair looks like I'm giving you the hump hairstyle of the early 2000s. It was a time.
The hump was definitely in the building.